<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InsideBhutan</string>
    <string name="photos_are_the_return_ticket_to_a_moment_otherwise_gone">Photos are the return ticket to a moment otherwise gone</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">appbar scrolling view behavior</string>
    <string name="phobjakha_valley">Location: Wangdue Phodrang, Bhutan
        Key attractions: Black-necked cranes migrate to Phobjikha from November, and the hike through the valleys to witness spectacular views of the birds and the amazing greenery.
        How to reach: Take a taxi to Wangdue from Thimphu or Phuentsholing. Then take a bus or shared cab from Wangdue to Phobjikha Valley.
        Places To Stay: The Valley Camp, Dewachen Hotel and Spa, Phuntsho Chholing Lodge, Gangtey Gonpa, Yue-Lo-Ki Guest Houes Gangtey</string>

    <string name="Talo_valley">Talo Village is one of the most beautiful places to see in Bhutan.
        You will agree once you visit. A perfect place for those who seek solace, Talo offers picturesque
        landscapes decorated with sweet corn and pea fields. At the very top, you will spot a Buddhist monastery.
        It is one of the top places to visit in Bhutan frequented by tourists. The landscape is complemented by snow-capped mountains.
        If you wish to explore Bhutan villages, then put this place on your itinerary.
        Location: Punakha, Bhutan</string>
    <string name="Bumdra_valley">Located at about 3800m above sea level, you can even camp in the cave that is called the ‘Cave of a Hundred Thousand Prayers’, and then end the trip with a visit to the beautiful Tiger’s Nest Monastery in Paro, making it all a one-of-a-kind spiritual and adventure experience.
        Location- Sang Choekhor, Paro, Bhutan</string>
    <string name="chimmi_lhakhang">The temple offers panoramic views of the Punakha Valley and overlooks beautiful paddy fields and a river that flows below the temple. You can take a short walk across paddy fields and villages to reach this temple. Chimi Lhakhang Temple is one of the most important places to visit in Bhutan.
        Location: The temple lies on the edge of the Lobesa valley on the confluence of the borders of Thimphu, Punakha and Wangduephodrang.
    </string>
    <string name="samtengang_track">Punakha and Wangdi valley, which are the location of this trek, is easily the best places to visit in Bhutan and that becomes evident as you depart from Punakha, getting views of some of the most amazing peaks of Jumolhari, Kang Bum Peak and the Tiger Mountain. What is even better is the fact that the recommended time of the year for this trek are the winter months, adding an additional note of beauty to the entire region.
        Location- Punakha and Wangdi Valley, Bhutan</string>
</resources>